Division of Paleobotany Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- George Wieland Archives, Series VIII
  - Miscellaneous; American Fossil Cycads., 001110
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 18, fig 4; C. dacotensis (minus flower bud), 001385
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 97, fig 4a; Raumeria, 001386
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 98; Raumeria, 001387
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 99, fig 6, 001388
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 101, fig 9b; Raumeria, 001389
    - Negatives. Raumeria x175, 001390
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Plate 107, fig A; C. dacotensis, 001391
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Text supp. B, fig 6; Raumeria reichenbachiana, 001392
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, Text supp. B, fig 6; Raumeria reichenbachiana, 001393
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX; Raumeria reichenbachiana, 001394
    - Negatives. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, fig 6; Raumeria reichenbachiana, 001395
    - Negatives. Raumeria, 001396
    - Negatives. Raumeria, 001397
    - Negatives. Raumeria, 001398
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea barti, Trans. ped., Of. quartz-druse lined cavity at level of a bract insertion, 001399
    - Negatives. C.f. Monaesthesia blanca; Cycadeoidea dartoni., 001400
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea painei (?), 001401
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea paynei, 001402
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea barti (about natural size), 001403
    - Negatives. C. wielandi, 001404
    - Negatives. Oolite 99%+SiO2, 001405
    - Negatives. Oolite 99%+SiO2, 001406
    - Negatives. Oolite Wieland, 001407
    - Negatives. Oolite Wieland, 001408
    - Negatives. Oolite Wieland, 001409
    - Negatives. Oolite Wieland, 001410
    - Negatives. Oolite x8, 001411
    - Negatives. Delevoryas & Jain; Paleontology; Vol. 10, part 4; December, 1967; Plate 92, fig 13; "A Middle Triassic flora from the Cacheuta Formation, Minas de Petroleo, Argentina; Rhatic Leaves, 001412
    - Negatives. Delevoryas & Jain; Paleontology; Vol. 10, part 4; December, 1967; Plate 97, fig 10; "A Middle Triassic flora from the Cacheuta Formation, Minas de Petroleo, Argentina; Rhatic Leaves, 001413
    - Negatives. Rhatic Leaves, 001414
    - Negatives. Rhatic Leaves, 001415
    - Negatives. Rhatic Leaves, 001416
    - Negatives. Rhatic Leaves, 001417
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001418
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001419
    - Negatives. S.1008; C. dartoni x100, 001420
    - Negatives. Wieland negative x175, 001421
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001422
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001423
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001424
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture; Metallographic plate, green rayfilter, Obj. 3, Oc. 4, Transmitted light, substage aplauntre condenser at brightest, Exposure 90 seconds, 001425
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001426
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture set, Picture 1 of 3, 001427
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture set, Picture 2 of 3, 001428
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture set, Picture 3 of 3, 001429
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001431
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001432
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001433
    - Negatives. Dion spinulomi x200, 001434
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture x175, 001435
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001436
    - Negatives. Drochodendron (25), 001437
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001438
    - Negatives. S. 1008; C. wartoni x100, 001439
    - Negatives. B. gibsonianus x 100, 001440
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001441
    - Negatives. Araucaria imbricata (39), 001442
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001443
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001444
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001445
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001446
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001447
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001448
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001449
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001450
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001451
    - Negatives. Cerro Cuadrado, Plate 14, fig. 4; Dioon spinulosum, 001452
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001453
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001454
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001455
    - Negatives. Cordaites, 001456
    - Negatives. Orbitolites marginalis, Orbitolite duplex (x2), 001457
    - Negatives. Cordaites laevis, 001458
    - Negatives. Dioon edule, 001459
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001460
    - Negatives. US Geological Survey, Monograph 48, Plate 20; Jurassic cycads from Oregon, 001461
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001462
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, fig. 66; A & B: G. biloba; C: G. huttoni, 001463
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Lepidodendron harcourti, 001464
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001465
    - Negatives. US Geological Survey, Monograph 14, Plate 12; Fig 1-6: 1. Baiera munsterana, 2. Pachyphyllum simile, 3. Pachyphyllum brevifolium, 4. Cheirolepis munsteri, 5. Phragma of Equisetum rogersi, 6. Clathropteris platyphylla, 001466
    - Negatives. Macrozamia moovei poisoned plant, 001467
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Assorted figures in Lichtdruck der Hofkunstanstalt, 001468
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Delta de Nil, 001469
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001470
    - Negatives. C. painei cambium, 001471
    - Negatives. US Geological Survey, Monograph 48, Plate 33; Jurassic Gingkos from Oregon, 001472
    - Negatives. Antholithus arberi, Gristhorpia nathorsti, 001473
    - Negatives. Psilophyton princeps, 001474
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001475
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001476
    - Negatives. Rhactic, Argentina(?), 001477
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001478
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001479
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001480
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001481
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001482
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001483
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001484
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001485
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001486
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001487
    - Negatives. Imprints of the Godwana System of India, Silicified in entirety, Black Hills, 001488
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001489
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001490
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001491
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001492
    - Negatives. US Geological Survey, Monograph 14, Plate 24; Figs 1-4: 1,2: Otozamite latior, 3: Otozamites breviflorius, 4: Cycadinocarpus chapini, 001493
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001494
    - Negatives. Fig 37, A-D; A,B: Neoropteris heterophylla, C: Neuropteridium validum, D: Linopteris brongniarti, 001495
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001496
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001497
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001498
    - Negatives. Voltzia heterophylla, 001499
    - Negatives. Tree stumps in a carboniferous forest. Negatives of F.S. Bradley, Nov. 5, 1914, 001500
    - Negatives. Carboniferous landscape- after Unger from a lantern slide; Negatives of F.S. Bradley, Nov. 5, 1914, 001501
    - Negatives. C. painei, 001502
    - Negatives. Pinus coultesi cone, 001503
    - Negatives. Parahydrospes paraionensis; good carapace, 001504
    - Negatives. T.3, C. marshiana; T.150, C. minnekahtensis, 001505
    - Negatives. Rhynic major; Asteroxylon maclioi; Phylogenetic Tree of Animal Kingdom, 001506
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea bibbinsi(?), 001507
    - Negatives. C. dakotensis, longitudinal type, Feb. 1921, 001508
    - Negatives. C. dakotensis, longitudinal type, Feb. 1921, 001509
    - Negatives. Cryptozoon, 001510
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001516
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001517
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001518
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001519
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001520
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001521
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001522
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001523
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001524
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001525
    - Negatives. Cycadeoidea dartoni, S. 938 x2, 001526
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001527
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001528
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001529
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001530
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001531
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001532
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001533
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001534
    - Negatives. Parahydroides paraionsis; good inside view of carapace, 001535
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001536
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001537
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001538
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001539
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001541
    - Negatives. Wieland negative, Miscellaneous picture, 001543
    - Prints. Palaeontographica, Band LXXXIX, 001228
    - Prints. Megaphyton photograph, 001328
    - Prints. Wieland; Cycadeoidea dactotensis, 001511
    - Prints. Wieland; Cycadeoidea colossalis, 001512
    - Prints. Photographs of Fossil Plants; Astromyleon, Calamostachys binneyana, Etapteris scottii, Lagenostoma ovoides, 001513
    - Prints. Rhaetic wing photos (x5); 15 July, 1940, 001514
    - Prints. Lepidodendron obovatum (photograph), 001515
  - Negatives. American fossil Cycads Volume 1., 001105
    - Negatives and Prints (x4). Vol I, Plate 22; Cycadeoidea Wielandi, 001316
    - Negatives. Plate 6; Simple stemmed and branched cycadeoidea trunks, 001107
    - Negatives. Plate 7; C. marshiana, T 164, 001109
    - Negatives. Plate 8, Figure 2, T. 1644; Cycadeoidea marshiana, 001111
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 12, T. 300; C. marshiana, 001112
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 13, T.300; Cycadeoidea marshiana, 001113
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate XLIII, G.R. Wieland Glass Slide, 001129
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 7, T. 164; Cycadeoiddea marshiana, 001181
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 7; C. marshiana, 001182
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 19, fig 6; Cycadeoidea foliage, 001183
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 19, T. 208, fig 7; Cycadeoidea foliage, 001184
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 19, T. 208, fig 8; Cycadeoidea foliage, 001185
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 25, S. 108, fig 6; Cycadeoidean ovulate strobili, 001186
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 34; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001187
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 44, fig 13; Cycas revoluta, 001188
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 45; Cycadocephalus sewardi and Cycadeoidean strobili, 001189
    - Negatives. Vol I, Page 65, fig 34; Trunk structure, 001190
    - Negatives. Vol I, Page 193, fig 106; Zamia floridana DC, 001191
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 36, S. 365, fig 2d; C. dacotensis, 001315
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 36, fig 2b, S. 367; C. dacotensis, 001317
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 9; C. superba, 001350
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 9; C. superba, 001351
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 36, S. 367, fig 2b; C. dacotensis, 001352
    - Negatives. Vol I, Plate 36, S. 367, fig 2c; C. dacotensis, 001353
    - Plates and Negative. Vol I, Plate 26, T.393 x4, S.393, 001118
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 8; Cycadeoidea marshiana, 001114
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 7; Cycadeoidea marshiana, 001115
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 40, fig 1; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001116
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 32, fig 7; Cycadeoidea Goucheriana Ward, 001117
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 103, fig 53; Zamia vroomi, 001119
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 161, fig 85; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001120
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 188, fig 101; Dion edule, 001121
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 192, fig 105; Zamia "glabra;" Vol I, Plate 196, fig 109; Zamia mexicana, is Ceratozamia mexicana in book, 001122
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 197, fig 110; Zamia Encephalartos altensteinii; Vol I, Plate 212; Zamia wallisii, 001123
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 203, fig 114; Cycos rumphi, 001124
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 204, fig 115; Neo-Caledonica; Vol I, Plate 207, fig 118; (Zamia) Encephalatos Ghellinckil, 001125
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 206, fig 117; Cyca media; Zamia lehmanni does not appear in Vol I, 001126
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 208, fig 119; Dion edule, 001127
    - Plates. Vol I, Plate 191, fig 104; Zamia roezli, 001128
  - Negatives. American fossil Cycads Volume 2., 001106
    - Negatives. Plate 20, Figure 1., 001108
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate I, figs 3, 4, 5; C. mirablilis Ledqueroux and C. marylandica Fontaine, 001130
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 3, fig 4; C. microphylla, 001131
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 3, T. 805, fig 1,2,3; Cycadeoidea Uddeni sp. nor, 001132
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 3, fig 5; C. microphylla, 001133
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 4; Piedmont Black Hawk Cycadecideas, 001134
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 4; Cycads from Minnekahta, S.D., 001135
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 5, fig 1,4. Piedmont Black Hawk C's. C. stilwelli, C. rhombica, 001136
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 5, T. 105, fig 2; Cycadeoidea stilwelli; Vol II, Plate 5, T. 630, fig 3; Cycadeoidea rhombica, 001137
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 5, T. 656, fig 5; Cycadeoidea sp., 001138
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 5, T. 656, fig 6; Cycadeoidea sp., 001139
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 6, T. 110, fig 1; Black Hawk Piedmont Series, C. Jenneyana, 001140
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 6, T. 110, fig 2; C. Jenneyana, 001141
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 6, T. 554, fig 3; C. Jenneyana, 001142
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 6, T. 642, fig 4; Cycadeoidea sp, 001143
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 7, T. 102, fig 1; Cycadeoidea Jenneyana, 001144
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 7, T. 117, fig 2; Cycadeoidea tingens, 001145
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 8; Cycadeoidea Jenneyana, 001146
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 9, T. 117; C. ingens, 001147
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 12, T. 122; C. ingens, 001148
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 12; C. ingens, 001149
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 15; C. colossalis, 001150
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 15, T. 2; C. colossalis, 001151
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate S.F.C, Cycadeoidea from Comanche, Texas photographed by Professor Petrikovich, 001152
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 21, T.140, fig 2. Cycadeoidea (minnekahtensis) marshiana (Wieland emend), 001153
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 21, T.140, fig 1. Cycadeoidea (minnekahtensis) marshiana, 001154
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 23, T.129; Cycadeoidea marshiana, 001155
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 24; C. marshiana, 001156
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 24, T.129; Cycadeoidea marshiana, 001157
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 24, T.129; Cycadeoidea marshiana, 001158
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 26, T. 3; C. marshiana, 001159
    - Negatives. Vol II, Page 85, T. 5, fig 35; Cycadeoidea paynei, 001160
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 38, T. 210; C. dartoni, 001161
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 39; C. dartoni, 001162
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 41; C. dartoni (type), 001164
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 42, fig 1; C. dartoni (type), 001165
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 44; C. dartoni (Type), 001167
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 1, fig 1; Cycadeoidea mirabilis, 001192
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 1, fig 1; Cycadeoidea mirabilis, 001193
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 1, fig 2; Cycadeoidea mirabilis, 001194
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 1, fig 2; Cycadeoidea mirabilis, 001195
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 20, T. 24, S. 927, fig 3; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001196
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 20, T. 24, S. 927, fig 3; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001197
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 20, T. 131, fig 5; Cycadeoidea wielandi, 001198
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 21, T. 140, fig 1; Cycadeoidea (minnekahtensis) marshiana, 001199
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 30, S. 981, fig 1; Cycadeoidea paynei, 001200
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 30, S. 981, fig 1; Cycadeoidea paynei, 001201
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 30, T. 377, S. 974, fig 2; Cycadeoidea sp., cf. nana, 001202
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 30, T. 377, S. 972, fig 3; Cycadeoidea sp., cf. nana, 001203
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 31, T. 393, S. 953, fig 3; Cycadeoidea wielandi, 001204
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 32, T. 737, fig 4; Cycadeoidea megalophylla, 001205
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 40, T. 210, S. 887, fig 1; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001206
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 40, T. 210, S. 878, fig 2; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001207
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 40, T. 210, S. 870, fig 4; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001208
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 40, T. 210, S. 858, fig 5; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001209
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 43; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001210
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 47, S. 983; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001211
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 52; Cycadeoidea wielandi, 001212
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 53, T. 481, fig 3; Cycadeoidea, 001213
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 55, T. 214, S. 82, fig 2; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001214
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 55, T. 214, S. 82, fig 2; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001215
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 56; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001216
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 56; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001217
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 56; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001218
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 56; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001219
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 62, fig 19; Cycadeoidea marshiana, 001220
    - Negatives. Vol II, Page 74, fig 27; Cycadeoidea colossalis, 001221
    - Negatives. Vol II, Page 84, T. 393, S. 709, fig 27; Cycadeoidea wielandi, 001222
    - Negatives. Vol II, Page 135, fig 48; Bennettites morierei type, 001223
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 49; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001318
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 49; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001319
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 212, fig 86; Zamia paucijuga, 001320
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 222, fig 92; Pachycereus grandis, 001321
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 54, fig 4; Seed of Lagenostoma ovoides, coal ball preparation, 001329
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 17, T. 24, bottom figure; Cycadeoidea dacotensis, 001360
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 25, T. 399, fig 4; Cycadeoidea marshiana, 001361
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 32, T. 77, S. 891, fig 1; Cycadeoidea wielandi, 001362
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 32, T. 77, S. 964, fig 2; Cycadeoidea wielandi, 001363
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 35, fig 4; Cycadeoidea paynei, 001364
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 40, T. 210, S. 858, fig 5; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001365
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 45, fig 5; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001366
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 49, S. 897, fig 1; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001367
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 52, T. 131, S. 909, fig 1; Cycadeoidea wielandi (?), 001368
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 52, T. 131, S. 909, fig 1; Cycadeoidea wielandi (?), 001369
    - Negatives. Vol II, Plate 57, S. 876, fig 3; Cycadeoidea colossalis, 001370
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 39, fig 10; C. jenneyana, 001163
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 43, fig 12; C. ingens, 001166
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 166, fig 60 B, C & D, Composite Seed Type, 001168
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 62, fig 19; C. marshiana, 001169
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 119, fig 40; Bennettites gibsonianus, 001170
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 137, fig 49; A-C: sp. (not Wielandi); B-C: Macbridei; C,D: B. gibsonianus; F,E: B. morierei, 001171
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 139, fig 50; A: C. dartoni; B: Physostoma; C: Lagenstoma lomaxi, 001172
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 142, fig 52; Cycadeoidea seed structure, 001173
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 149, fig 56; Diagrammatic drawings of diverse types of ancient seeds, 001174
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 196, fig 77; Williamsonia gigas, 001175
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 196, fig 78; Williamsonia gigas, 001176
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 201, fig 79 A-E; A,B,D,E: Williamsonia netzahualcoyotl wieland; C: Williamsonia nathorstii wieland, 001177
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 186, fig 72; Wialliamsonia sp., 001178
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 194, fig 76B; Williamsonia gigas, 001179
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 174, fig 64A,B; Williamsonia gigas, 001180
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 125, fig 43; Cycadeoidea reichenbachiana, 001371
    - Prints. Vol II, Plate 133, fig 46c; Cycadeoidea dartoni, 001372